Coordonnées

Casablanca Aine sbaa 0684134782 (Home) taffahachraf184@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/achraf-taffahb679a01aa (LinkedIn)

Principales compétences

Gestion d'équipe Compétences analytiques HTML

Certifications

Problem Solving (Intermediate) Certificate

NDG LINUX ESSENTIALS

Node (Basic)

Java (Basic) Certificate

M001: MongoDB Basics

Achraf TAFFAH

Software engineering student

Casablanca, Casablanca-Settat, Maroc

Résumé

Hi, I'm Achraf TAFFAH, a passionate self-taught full-stack web developer and a freelance software engineer from morocco. my passion for software lies with dreaming up ideas and making them come true with elegant interfaces. I take great care in the experience, architecture, and code quality of the things I build.

Expérience

N7Geeks

1 an 5 mois

Vice-président septembre 2022 - Present (5 mois)

Mohammedia, Casablanca-Settat, Maroc

Responsable de formation

septembre 2021 - Present (1 an 5 mois)

Mohammedia, Casablanca-Settat, Maroc

Formation

ENSET Mohammedia

Génie du Logiciel et des Systèmes Informatiques Distribués · (septembre 2021 - septembre 2024)

Lycée technique Chichaoua

Brevet de technicien supérieur (B.T.S.), Multimedia et conception web · (septembre 2019 - septembre 2021)

Lycée el baroudi

Baccalauréat scientifique, Sciences physiques · (septembre 2018 - septembre 2019)